(Howard:)laser-equipped
surveillance satellite.
(Sheldon:)Excuse me.
(Sheldon:)If we're changing topics,
I believe I have first dibs
(Sheldon:)with capybara, a rodent
the size of a baby hippo.
(Leonard:)Congratulations,
Howard.
(Howard:)Thanks.
(Howard:)Listen, I have to get
a security clearance,
(Howard:)so you guys might be
hearing from the FBI.
(Raj:)Whoa, whoa, whoa!
(Raj:)I don't want to speak
to the FBI.
(Leonard:)Why not?
(Raj:)I'm brown and I talk funny.
(Howard:)They're just doing
a background check on me.
It doesn't matter;
they'll find a reason
(Raj:)to give me a one-way ticket
back to Gandhi-ville.
(Raj:)By the way,
(Raj:)when I say that,
it's not offensive.
(Leonard:)Don't be ridiculous, Raj.
(Leonard:)You're here legally.
(Raj:)Nobody cares.
Do you know how long it's been
(Raj:)since I got through
airport security
(Raj:)without being given
a colonoscopy?
(Sheldon:)You know, I
try very hard
(Sheldon:)to make our lunch hours
educational and informative,
(Sheldon:)but your insistence on
talking about your own lives
(Sheldon:)stymies me at
every turn.
(Leonard:)Fine, Sheldon, tell us
about your giant rodents.
1No, you squandered
your time with me,
(Sheldon:)and the moment
has now passed.
(Sheldon:)Feast on your disappointment,
(Sheldon:)much as the capybara
feasts on its own waste.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪